Tufts University International Newsletter UP183
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University International Newsletter
1976 -- 1989
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
International Center
UP183
0.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes the newsletter for international students, with information on events and activities specifically for them.
Biographical / Historical
Since the 1950s, the International Center has facilitated college-wide intercultural exchange. The Center staff works to raise intercultural awareness, to increase the knowledge of immigration laws affecting the Tufts international community, and to advocate a campus climate that respects cultural differences.
- Tufts University International Newsletter, 1976 -- 1989; UP183.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes the newsletter for international students, with information on events and activities specifically for them.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1976-01; UP183.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1976-04; UP183.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1976-05; UP183.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1976-10; UP183.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1977-02; UP183.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1977-03; UP183.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1977-05; UP183.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1978-04; UP183.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1978-01; UP183.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1978-05; UP183.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1978-09; UP183.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1978-11; UP183.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1978-12; UP183.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1979-01; UP183.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1979-03; UP183.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1979-05; UP183.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Tufts International Newsletter, 1979-10; UP183.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1979-11; UP183.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1980-02; UP183.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1980-03; UP183.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1980-04; UP183.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1980-09; UP183.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1980-10; UP183.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1980-11; UP183.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1981-01; UP183.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1981-03; UP183.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1981-04; UP183.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1981-10; UP183.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1981-12; UP183.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1982-02; UP183.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1982-03; UP183.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1982-11; UP183.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1982-12; UP183.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1983-02; UP183.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1983-04; UP183.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1983-10; UP183.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1983-12; UP183.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1984-03; UP183.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1985-03; UP183.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1985-09; UP183.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1985-10; UP183.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1986-01; UP183.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1986-08; UP183.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1986-10; UP183.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1986-12; UP183.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1987-02; UP183.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1987-11; UP183.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1988-03; UP183.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1988-12; UP183.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1989-02; UP183.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1989-03; UP183.001.001.00051 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1989-04; UP183.001.001.00052 (Box 1)